

# Ijasrahman Melevilakkathil

Flutter Developer

Mobile App Developer with 2+ years of experience in developing cross-platform applications using Flutter. I have gained an in-depth understanding of the main mobile platforms and recognize the subtle differences between each. Ability to take new challenges and tasks and find solutions for the same.

#### $\searrow$

ijasmv98@gmail.com



+91 7559842640



Kerala, India



www.ijasmv.ml



linkedin.com/in/ijasmv

#### **SKILLS**

Flutter

UI/UX

C#

Android App

Photoshop

Figma

Adobe XD

**LANGUAGES** 

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Elementary Proficiency

Elementary Proficiency

Limited Working Proficiency

Dart

HTML

Enalish

Arabic

Tamil

Hindi

Malayalam

CSS

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Senior Flutter Developer

#### Microzys

07/2022 - Present

- Developed accounting related multi platform apps.
- Integrated flutter apps with gRPC server backend.
- Developed company website with Flutter web.
- Took responsibilities of company related to development.
- Implemented MVVM architecture, providers, sqflite, etc.

## Flutter Developer

#### Cookee Apps Llp

10/2020 - 07/2022

- Design and implement new app modules based on the project requirements using Flutter framework.
- Completed more than 20 projects in Flutter.
- UI designing and prototype building based on requirements.
- Trained 2 freshers as Flutter developers.
- Implemented bloc, google maps, push notifications, providers, payment gateways, deep-linking, REST APIs etc.

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

Mark Messenger (09/2018 - 10/2018)

- Windows application for Tuition Centers to send student's marks as SMS to parents.
- C#, SQL.

Online Guide (03/2022 - 05/2022)

- Study assisstance for online tuition.
- Study materials, daily prayer marking, points, etc.

#### 5000y ....cca...c.a, ca...y

**EDUCATION** 

# **B.E. Computer Science and Engineering**

JCT College of Engineering and Technology

2016 - 2020

Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India

#### **INTERESTS**

Coding

Editing

Photography

## **FLUTTER PROJECTS**

E commerce App, Visitor management system, Appointment Booking App, Donation App for NGO, Logistics app, Invoice app, etc.